{
    "subject": "Fox_Crane",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kay_Bennett",
    "human_readable": "Fox Crane is married to Kay Bennett.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882381558418274,
            "question": "Is Kay Bennett married to Fox Crane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9785377979278564,
            "question": "Is there a marital relationship between Fox Crane and Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624856114387512,
            "question": "Are Fox Crane and Kay Bennett a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8966538310050964,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Fox Crane and Kay Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8694685101509094,
            "question": "Who is Fox Crane married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8643072843551636,
            "question": "To whom is Kay Bennett married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8542155623435974,
            "question": "Who is Kay Bennett married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7369595766067505,
            "question": "Name Fox Crane's spouse."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6217514872550964,
            "question": "What is the name of Fox Crane's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3666461110115051,
            "question": "What is the name of Fox Crane's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fox Crane is married to Kay Bennett.",
            "html": "yago_30079_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Fox Crane's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30079_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name Fox Crane's spouse.",
            "html": "yago_30079_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Kay Bennett married to?",
            "html": "yago_30079_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30079_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention that Fox Crane and Kay Bennett are married. In fact, the documents indicate that Kay Bennett married Fox Crane on January 10, 2007, but they also provide details of a potential separation or plans for separation, suggesting that they may not be currently married as of the last update provided in the context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Kay Bennett married Fox Crane on January 10, 2007, as stated in context information 3 and 4. Furthermore, her status as his wife is reinforced by the mention of their son Brian Lopez-Fitzgerald, who was born to Kay and Miguel after their marriage. Therefore, at no point in the provided context is Fox Crane ever mentioned as being married to Kay Bennett; rather, they are portrayed as a couple with children together.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}